const STORE = {
  questions: [//1

    {
      number: 1,
      question: "What is the illuminati?",
      options: [
        "A secret society that controls and influences the world economically, culturally, and conspires to control world affairs",
        "a type of spaghetti",
        "It is a rapper named Jay-Z",
        "the celebrity, Kim Kardashian"
      ],
      answer: "A secret society that controls and influences the world economically, culturally, and conspires to control world affairs"
    },
    //2
    {
      number: 2,
      question: "What is a sign someone is a reptilian or has reptilian DNA?",
      options: [
          "They can shapeshift, their iris' in their eyes will be like slits, they seem to have no soul, little conscious awareness, and a lack of empathy",
          "They live off a strict diet of only eggs",
          "they go to Starbucks every day",
          "they are simply cluster-b personalities with antisocial personality disorder and psychopathic traits"
      ],
      answer: "They can shapeshift, their iris' in their eyes will be like slits, they seem to have no soul, little conscious awareness, and a lack of empathy"
    },
    //3
    {
      number: 3,
      question: "What is the mandela effect?",
      options: [
          "when people get dizzy after being around too much wifi",
          "when people start hearing voices",
          "what happens when someone has a clear memory of something that never happend in this reality",
          "psychosis"
      ],
      answer: "what happens when someone has a clear memory of something that never happend in this reality"
    },
    //4
    {
      number: 4,
      question: "which option is an example of the Mandela effect?	", 
      options: [
          "people believe Jif peanut butter used to be called Jiffy",
          "The cartoon 'Looney Toons' used to be spelled as 'Looney Tunes'",
          "The monopoly man from the board game used to wear a monocle",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      answer: "All of the above"
    },
    //5
    {
      number: 5,
      question: "What is an issue with time travel?",
      options: [
          "humans or animals being sent to a different period in time can come back with different parts of their bodies distorted",
          "pictures and photographs tend to get distorted",
          "cause and effect will distort periods in time",
          "all of the above"
      ],
      answer: "all of the above"
    },
    //6
    {
      number: 6,
      question: 'What is the name that describes when government agents make use of electromagnetic radiation such as the microwave auditory effect to transmit sounds and thoughts into people\'s heads as a form of harassment?',
      options: [
          "This doesn't happen. These people are just crazy and experiencing hallucinations",
          "cyber bullying",
          "target individuals or TI's",
          "tinfoil-hat-people"
      ],
      answer: "target individuals or TI's"
    },
    //7
    {
      number: 7,
      question: "What is the pracice of being able to seek impressions about a distant or unseen target called by using extrasensory perception(ESP) of the mind?", 
      options: [
          "telepathy",
          "precognition",
          "remote viewing (RV)",
          "clairaudience"   
      ],
      answer: "remote viewing (RV)"
    },
    //8
    {
      number: 8,
      question: "What is HAARP?",
      options: [
          "secret weapon disguised as a weather research facility program that can control the weather and induce earthquakes",
          "a facility that analyzes the ionosphere to investigate potential for ionospheric technology for radio communications and surveillance",
          "a device that can erase your memory disguised as a musical instrument",
          "a pyramid on Mars"
      ], 
      answer: "secret weapon disguised as a weather research facility program that can control the weather and induce earthquakes"
    },
    //9
    {
      number: 9,
      question: "What do people take as a sign the moon is hollow?",
      options: [
          "it's translucent when sunlight shines through it",
          "when Apollo 12 deliberately crashed its Lunar Module onto the Moon's surface, the moon rang like a bell for over an hour",
          "because it looks a lot like the death star weapon from the Star Wars movie, except it is just disguised with rocks and dust",
          "The craters look like entrances into the center of the moon"
      ], 
      answer: "when Apollo 12 deliberately crashed its Lunar Module onto the Moon's surface, the moon rang like a bell for over an hour"
    },
    //10
    {
      number: 10,
      question: "What is the term for describing an intentional out-of-body experience where you are capable of traveling throughout the universe through your \"astral body\"?",
      options: [
          "time traveling",
          "kundelini awakening",
          "lucid dreaming",
          "astral projection"
      ], 
      answer: "astral projection"
    },
    
  ],
  questionNumber: 0,
  score: 0
};